# **Eric Martin**



eric martin@me.com



(919) 272-2201



linkedin.com/in/eric-martin-292b4770

# Summary

Experienced Lead in Technical and Customer Support with 10+ years of experience. Created short term and long term plans revolving around specific customers and employees based on needs, including a personalized customer support representative for Gogo's largest customer. Created and implemented a role's schedule for Gogo's Activations team to ensure higher quality work, and to maximize efficiency with customer contact. Resulting in achieving 150% of Executive Leadership driven metrics.

# **Experience**



# Activations/Tier 1 Customer Support Team Lead

Gogo Business Aviation

Jul 2018 - Present (3 years 3 months +)

Partner with the Technical Support Manager in providing quality and efficient customer service.

Responsible for prioritizing daily workload, problem solving, training, scheduling and reward/recognition programs.

Lead the Activations/Tier 1 Representative teams, ensuring high quality support. Manager of day to day operations for the teams.

Ensures continuous improvement and management of team to ensure the same high level of professionalism and quality support services for which Gogo is known.

## Tier 1 Support Representative

Gogo Business Aviation

Aug 2016 - Jul 2018 (2 years)

Provided the most efficient and high quality customer and technical support to Gogo Business Aviation customers (OEMs, Dealers and Aircraft Owners/Operators) for all account administrative tasks and Tier 1 level trouble shooting to include equipment configuration and system activation verifications.



# **Customer Care Engineer**

Granicus

Jan 2015 - Aug 2016 (1 year 8 months)

Provided client support and technical issue resolution via E-Mail, phone and other electronic medium for our clients as well as provided training to clients in the use of company systems and applications.

Monitored the health of our clients' solutions using our Proactive Systems Management tools and responded to client requests within a maximum of two hours.

Maintained/modified web-based documents written in HTML/CSS & Smarty code.

Documented procedures taken identifying/resolving client issues in our Salesforce CRM database.

Provided networking troubleshooting and provided superior customer service.

# Apple Technician

#### Apple

Aug 2008 - Jan 2015 (6 years 6 months)

Responsible for handling repairs and replacements of Apple Products. Including but not limited to troubleshooting, diagnosis of Apple computers, and making necessary repairs according to Apple checks and procedures.

Responsible for troubleshooting various network issues including VPN settings and Outlook.

Performed data migrations from computer to computer, both PC and Mac.

Responsible for installing operating systems and applications on computers.

Accustom to handling a high volume of duties every day, and maintaining a high quality work product.

Continually involved in training of all Apple product knowledge and handling.

### **Education**



# UNIV University of Nevada-Las Vegas

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Film

2005 - 2012

Was a student leader for Intervarsity Christian Fellowship for four years.



# Wakefield High School

High School, General 2000 - 2004

# **Licenses & Certifications**



Transitioning from Manager to Leader - Lynda.com



Balancing Multiple Roles as a Leader - Lynda.com



in Learn the Process of Effective Leadership - LinkedIn

#### Skills

Troubleshooting • Customer Satisfaction • Microsoft Office • Problem Solving • Process Improvement • Leadership • Team Leadership • Time Management

# **Honors & Awards**



I received the Eagle Scout Award at age 16.